const e="We could not find what you asked for, but got you this",i="insurance",o=200,t=120,a=[{id:259,question:"When an insured person admits that he has been indemnified, he means that",option:{a:"the insurance company has accepted his claims",b:"the damaged property has been recovered",c:"He has paid his premium",d:"the insurance company has restored him to his former position"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"5"},{id:55,question:"A  statement  of  fact  that  the insured must have an interest in the object of the contract is called",option:{a:"warranty",b:"insurable interest",c:"subrogation",d:"object interest"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"1"},{id:318,question:"The policy that covers  an  insured  employee  against injury  sustained  in  the  course  of  employment  is",option:{a:"professional indemnity",b:"product liability",c:"public liability",d:"employer’s liability"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2015"},{id:247,question:"Third party provides cover only for damages to",option:{a:"assurer",b:"insurer",c:"2nd party",d:"another person"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"4"},{id:150,question:"The legal right to insure a subject matter is",option:{a:"Indemnity",b:"Subject Matter",c:"Subrogation",d:"Insurable interest"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"2"},{id:170,question:"The type of questionnaire drawn up by   insurers, requesting certain information to assess risk is --------- form",option:{a:"Acceptance",b:"Compensation",c:"Credit",d:"Proposal"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"3"},{id:14,question:"Abandonment is mostly applicable to",option:{a:"marine insurance",b:"motor insurance",c:"fire insurance",d:"engineering insurance"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2014"},{id:177,question:"Any circumstance that promotes the probability of a loss is called",option:{a:"Accident",b:"Hazard",c:"Loss",d:"Risk"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"3"},{id:200,question:"Another name for an insured in a life insurance contract is",option:{a:"Insurer",b:"Assured",c:"Assurer",d:"Agent"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"3"},{id:176,question:"The person  that  brings  an  insurance  contract into existence  between  the principal  and  third  party is a/an",option:{a:"Agent",b:"Bailee",c:"Contractor",d:"Insurer"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"3"},{id:348,question:"The principle of maritime law which makes owners of a ship and cargo share in a loss incurred voluntarily is",option:{a:"special average",b:"general average",c:"specific average",d:"particular average"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2015"},{id:251,question:"Insurance premium depends on the",option:{a:"amount of profit to be made by the insurer",b:"various insurance companies in a place",c:"extent of the possible loss and the frequency of risk",d:"supply and demand"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"5"},{id:45,question:"The consideration paid for insurance contract is",option:{a:"money",b:"commission",c:"premium",d:"fee"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2014"},{id:236,question:"Which of the method below can be used to provide indemnity in the event of loss",option:{a:"moral advice",b:"resolution of policy",c:"cash payment",d:"professional encouragement"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"4"},{id:267,question:"One of this is the consideration paid for insurance contract",option:{a:"fee",b:"cheque",c:"commission",d:"premium"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"5"},{id:315,question:"Which  of  the  following  would  not  give  cause  for subrogation right?",option:{a:"Benefit",b:"Contract",c:"Statute",d:"Salvage"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2015"},{id:29,question:"A provision in a policy that exempts an insurer from liability if the loss is less than a certain amount is",option:{a:"excess",b:"transfer",c:"lay days",d:"franchise"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2014"},{id:321,question:"A policy taken for full protection against fire and other risks such as flood, tempest, riot and civil commotion is",option:{a:"consequential loss",b:"fire and all risks policy",c:"combined householder’s policy",d:"fire and special perils"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2015"},{id:96,question:"“Hull” in marine policy refers to the",option:{a:"boiler",b:"cost of transporting the goods",c:"goods on board",d:"ship"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"1"},{id:178,question:"Indemnity is provided through the following media except",option:{a:"Cash",b:"Commission",c:"Reinstatement",d:"Repair"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"3"},{id:38,question:"Effective supervision and licensing of insurance firms in Nigeria is the function of",option:{a:"National Insurance Commission",b:"Institute of Loss Adjusters of Nigeria",c:"Chartered Insurance Institute of Nigeria",d:"Nigerian Corporation of Registered Insurance Brokers"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2014"},{id:262,question:"One of this is a method of claim settlement",option:{a:"price",b:"trade by barter",c:"exchange",d:"cash"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"5"},{id:120,question:"An application form which is filled by anyone taking out an insurance policy is called",option:{a:"A policy form",b:"A claim form",c:"A proposal form",d:"Proximate cause form"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"2"},{id:197,question:"Person who makes claim is called",option:{a:"Claimant",b:"Client",c:"Insured",d:"Insurer"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"3"},{id:235,question:"Proposal form is not applicable to the following except",option:{a:"aviation",b:"engineering",c:"large risk of fire",d:"fidelity guarantee"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"4"},{id:124,question:"Cover note usually run for about",option:{a:"One month",b:"Two days",c:"5 years",d:"3 days"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"2"},{id:59,question:"In insurance contract offeree is the",option:{a:"insured",b:"insurance company",c:"client",d:"Third party"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"1"},{id:141,question:"The acronym “CllN” refers to",option:{a:"Certified insurance institute",b:"Certified insured institute",c:"Certified international institute",d:"Chartered insurance institute"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"2"},{id:199,question:"The policy that provides protection for goods or cargoes and ships against the perils of the sea is",option:{a:"Fire",b:"Marine",c:"Aviation",d:"Credit"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"3"},{id:208,question:"An undertaking by the insured that certain things shall be done or not be done or certain things shall be put in place or not in place is called",option:{a:"warranties and representation",b:"utmost good faith and uberrimae fidei",c:"insurable and non-insurable",d:"subrogation and indemnity"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"4"},{id:295,question:"Business interruption insurance can also be called",option:{a:"consequential loss",b:"constructive loss",c:"partial  loss",d:"general loss"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"5"},{id:30,question:"Which of the following policies is a peril covered under a standard fire policy?",option:{a:"Lightning",b:"Storm",c:"Civil commotion",d:"Escape of oil"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2014"},{id:159,question:"The price of insurance is known as",option:{a:"Rate",b:"Interest",c:"Premium",d:"Profit"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"3"},{id:216,question:"With assurance contract there is",option:{a:"uncertainly of reward",b:"certainty of reward",c:"certainty of occurrence",d:"uncertainty of occurrence"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"4"},{id:56,question:"A fundamental condition which must be filled  by the  insured for compensation is",option:{a:"warranty",b:"obligation",c:"interest",d:"premium"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"1"},{id:309,question:"A new Nissan car valued at N= 350,000 was used to replace a Peugeot car with a sum insured N= 250.000 in private policy. The Peugeot car enjoys a 25% no claim discount. If the rate of premium is 11% and the no claim discount is transferred to the  new vehicle, what  would be the premium for the new Nissan car?",option:{a:"N= 20,625",b:"N= 27,500",c:"N= 28,875",d:"N= 38,500"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2015"},{id:278,question:"Physical loss of limbs or total blindness injury is an example of",option:{a:"permanent disablement",b:"temporary disablement",c:"mid-term disablement",d:"total disablement"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"5"},{id:250,question:"The deliberate throwing overboard of part of a cargo without a good intention is called",option:{a:"jettison",b:"barratry",c:"voyaging",d:"overboard"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"4"},{id:83,question:"The  principle  of  insurance  which  states  that a person must be in a legally recognized relationship to what is  insured  such  that  he  will  benefit  from its existence or suffer by its loss is",option:{a:"utmost good faith",b:"insurable interest",c:"proximate cause",d:"subrogation"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"1"},{id:248,question:"The type of cover for violent and forcible entry into a premises is called",option:{a:"burglary and theft",b:"third party fire and theft",c:"third party and theft",d:"stealing"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"4"},{id:317,question:"A clause in an insurance policy that makes a claim jointly payable to the policyholder and the third party is",option:{a:"claim clause",b:"mortgagee clause",c:"mortgage clause",d:"joint liability clause"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2015"},{id:134,question:"A house worth N=60,000 insured against fire for N=40,000.  Fire destroyed and cause damage worth N=30,000. On the house under which insurance principle will the owner be entitled to compensation of N=30,000.",option:{a:"Contribution",b:"Subrogation",c:"indemnity",d:"Uberrimae fidei"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"2"},{id:183,question:"Which of these is insurable?",option:{a:"Fire",b:"Inflation",c:"Bad publicity",d:"Riot and war"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"3"},{id:20,question:"A residential building built beside a petrol filling station is described as a",option:{a:"risk",b:"hazard",c:"peril",d:"liability"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2014"},{id:332,question:"One of the benefits payable under personal accident insurance policy is",option:{a:"retirement benefit",b:"surrender benefit",c:"death benefit",d:"transfer benefit"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2015"},{id:229,question:"One of the following is a condition for contribution",option:{a:"bilateral interest",b:"multilatual interest",c:"two subject matter",d:"common subject matter"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"4"},{id:113,question:"A peril is best defined as",option:{a:"Chance of a loss",b:"The occurrence of a loan",c:"The cause of a loss",d:"The result of a loss"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"2"},{id:221,question:"A contract which has no legal effect is called",option:{a:"voidable contract",b:"legal contract",c:"void contract",d:"valid contract"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"4"},{id:71,question:"The uncertainty as to the occurrence of a loos is",option:{a:"Hazard",b:"Loss",c:"Risk",d:"insurance"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"1"},{id:205,question:"The coming together of minds of  the two parties to the insurance contract is called",option:{a:"surrender value",b:"acceptance",c:"consensus ad-idem",d:"adhesion"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"4"},{id:136,question:"The amount given to the insured if he does not want the contract to continue is called",option:{a:"Insurance broker",b:"Premium",c:"Surrender value",d:"Assessor loss adjuster"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"2"},{id:330,question:"The amount payable to an insured in the event of fire damage of household items is the",option:{a:"cost of repair",b:"actual cash value",c:"replacement cost",d:"sum insured"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2015"},{id:290,question:"Marine insurance policy which covers all the ship or vessels belonging to one owner is",option:{a:"flect policy",b:"mixed policy",c:"value policy",d:"fixed policy"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"5"},{id:42,question:"A voucher signed by the insured before collecting his claim is",option:{a:"money collect receipt",b:"discharge voucher",c:"payment receipt",d:"pay - in - slip"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2014"},{id:43,question:"To which of the following parties does the principle of utmost good faith apply in a contract of insurance?",option:{a:"The proposer only",b:"The insurer only",c:"The insurer and proposer",d:"The third party and insured"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2014"},{id:26,question:"An insurer who buys reinsurance cover is insured as",option:{a:"retrocession",b:"retrocedant",c:"cession",d:"cadent"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2014"},{id:21,question:"The document that sets out the list of items covered in insurance is a",option:{a:"manifest",b:"bill of lading",c:"policy list",d:"policy specification or form"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2014"},{id:324,question:"Insurance is described as a risk",option:{a:"avoidance mechanism",b:"regulating mechanism",c:"transfer mechanism",d:"assessment mechanism"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2015"},{id:179,question:"The policy that covers loss of cash while in transit or at home is --------------- insurance",option:{a:"Burglary",b:"Business interruption",c:"Credit",d:"Money"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"3"},{id:244,question:"The process of transferring risk from one insurer to another is called",option:{a:"contribution",b:"re-insurance",c:"re-processing",d:"re-activating"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"4"},{id:299,question:"The party who proposes to the insurance company to insure his properly is called",option:{a:"offeree",b:"offeror",c:"acceptance party",d:"offer client"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"5"},{id:87,question:"The principle of insurance which states that the insure should be truthful and disclose all material fact is",option:{a:"subrogation",b:"utmost good faith",c:"indemnity",d:"insurable interest"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"1"},{id:226,question:"Another name for utmost good faith",option:{a:"expirit - de - corps",b:"uberrimae fidei",c:"caveat emptor",d:"proximate cause"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"4"},{id:206,question:"Uberrimae fidei is equally known as",option:{a:"contract",b:"agreement",c:"consensus",d:"utmost good faith"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"4"},{id:114,question:"One of the essential features of insurance contract is",option:{a:"Premium",b:"Subrogation",c:"Interest",d:"Disclosure"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"2"},{id:169,question:"A customer that suffers loss or sustain injury while using a business outfit that belongs to another perosn, can sue the property owner under -------------- insurance",option:{a:"Professional indemnity",b:"Public liability",c:"Employers’ liability",d:"Personal accident"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"3"},{id:325,question:"A fire insurance policy valued at N= 250,000 is issued at the rate of 0.2%. How much would the premium be, if the policy is granted with 5% long - term agreement discount?",option:{a:"N= 475",b:"N= 500",c:"N= 12,500",d:"N= 13,000"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2015"},{id:53,question:"An insurance principle that requires the insured to be honest and disclose all relevant facts is called",option:{a:"subrogation",b:"utmost good faith",c:"proximate cause",d:"insurable interest"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"1"},{id:223,question:"Which of the following cannot enter into an insurance contract?",option:{a:"adult",b:"insured",c:"minor",d:"insurer"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"4"},{id:116,question:"The principle that requires the insured to disclose to the insurer all matters relating to the object of insurance is called",option:{a:"Uberrimae fidei",b:"Proximate cause",c:"Abandonment",d:"Subrogation"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"2"},{id:323,question:"A clause in marine insurance policy prohibiting the insured from giving up a damaged property is",option:{a:"deductible",b:"abandonment",c:"indemnity",d:"compensation"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2015"},{id:107,question:"Insurance was developed as a result of the existence of",option:{a:"Hazards",b:"Loss",c:"Risk",d:"Indemnity"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"2"},{id:185,question:"In insurance contract, failure to disclose all relevant material facts will render the contract",option:{a:"legal",b:"Voidable",c:"Void",d:"Implied"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"3"},{id:66,question:"Insured is likewise known as",option:{a:"insuree",b:"Insurer",c:"policy holder",d:"contractor"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"1"},{id:157,question:"------------ is used to bring amendment in a policy that is either to add in a new thing or removal of an existing thing in the policy",option:{a:"Excess",b:"Endorsement",c:"Claim form",d:"Policy"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"3"},{id:39,question:"The payment made when the insured is  not  entitled to claim under a policy is",option:{a:"voluntary excess",b:"ex-gratia",c:"return premium",d:"premium"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2014"},{id:52,question:"An  insurance  feature  that  requires  the  parties  to disclose  all  material  facts  about  the  agreement is known as",option:{a:"Adhesion",b:"Disclosure",c:"Material fact",d:"Utmost good faith"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"1"},{id:156,question:"A temporary certificate to show that a cover is in existence is called",option:{a:"Policy",b:"Certificate",c:"Cover note",d:"Claim slip"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"3"},{id:306,question:"Which of the following is the function of a loss adjuster?",option:{a:"Ensures payment of adequate compensation",b:"Advises the insurer on claim",c:"Operates with unlimited authority",d:"Notifies insurer of the loss"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2015"},{id:92,question:"Another name for business interruption insurance is",option:{a:"property insurance",b:"consequential loss",c:"credit insurance",d:"excess loss"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"1"},{id:282,question:"The periodic payment made by the insured to the insurer as financial cost of obtaining insurance",option:{a:"annuity",b:"premium",c:"claim",d:"dividend"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"5"},{id:283,question:"The amount added to the standard premium in respect of the larger than standard risk presented by the proposer is called",option:{a:"premium increase",b:"premium loading",c:"premium payment",d:"premium commission"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"5"},{id:1,question:"Which of the following policies will prevent loss of home if the wage earner dies?",option:{a:"Term assurance",b:"Endowment assurance",c:"Mortgage insurance",d:"Whole life assurance"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2014"},{id:253,question:"Payment by the insurer to the insured out of sympathy is known as",option:{a:"utmost good faith",b:"proximate cause",c:"peril",d:"ex-gratia payment"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"5"},{id:256,question:"Another name for the assured is",option:{a:"insurance company’s client",b:"insurance broker",c:"insurance company",d:"insurance agent"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"5"},{id:32,question:"A contract sold  by  insurance companies that  pay  a monthly or  quarterly income  benefit for the  life  of a person is",option:{a:"endowment",b:"annuity",c:"income",d:"freight"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2014"},{id:67,question:"Insurance contract is between",option:{a:"Broker and Agent",b:"Insured and Insurer",c:"Insurer  and Agent",d:"Insured and Agent"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"1"},{id:186,question:"Any information that will influence a prudent insurer is called",option:{a:"contract",b:"misrepresentation",c:"disclosure",d:"Material facts"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"3"},{id:65,question:"The following are exempted from a contract because they do not have the contractual capacity except",option:{a:"Drunkard",b:"Alien",c:"Mental patient",d:"Adult"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"1"},{id:162,question:"The essential value of valid contract that states that the parties to a contract must be in perfect agreement and have a common mind is",option:{a:"Consideration",b:"Perpetual existence",c:"Excess",d:"Consensus ad-idem"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"3"},{id:257,question:"One of the following is legally used by the insured while the policy is being processed",option:{a:"indemnity form",b:"claim form",c:"cover note",d:"proposal form"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"5"},{id:190,question:"When an   insurer agrees   to   replace   irreparably damaged or stolen goods with similar type it is called",option:{a:"Reinstatement",b:"Cash",c:"Repairs",d:"Replacement"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"3"},{id:147,question:"An insurance cover for lawyers, accountants and brokers is",option:{a:"Employment",b:"Professional",c:"Public",d:"Product"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"2"},{id:322,question:"The  person  that   transfers  risks  to  the  insurance company is called",option:{a:"a broker",b:"an insured",c:"an underwriter",d:"a loss adjuster"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2015"},{id:8,question:"The evidence of the insurance contract is",option:{a:"proposal form",b:"policy",c:"schedule",d:"endorsement"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2014"},{id:335,question:"Who  among  the  following  is  an  employer  of  loss adjuster?",option:{a:"Insurer",b:"Broker",c:"Insured",d:"Agent"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2015"},{id:146,question:"Workman compensation is also referred to as",option:{a:"Fidelity insurance",b:"Employment liability",c:"Public liability",d:"Product liability"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"2"},{id:33,question:"George effected two personal accident policies. The first policy provides N= 25,000.00 cover for loss of limb. The second policy provides N= 30,000.00 cover for loss of limb. What is the total amount that  George  will receive in the event of a valid loss of limb claim?",option:{a:"N= 5,000.00",b:"N= 25,000.00",c:"N= 30,000.00",d:"N= 55,000.00"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2014"},{id:69,question:"The seller of insurance product is",option:{a:"Insurer",b:"Insured",c:"Broker",d:"Agent"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"1"},{id:46,question:"The alternative to seeking for surrender value in a life assurance contract is",option:{a:"automatic non - forfeiture",b:"revival condition",c:"paid-up policy",d:"standing order"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2014"},{id:313,question:"Which class of life assurance would a young couple who desires to start a new business in five years time purchase?",option:{a:"Whole life policy",b:"Limited whole life policy",c:"Keyman policy",d:"Endowment policy"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2015"},{id:338,question:"The amount charged when a ship overstays at the port under a marine contract is",option:{a:"penalty",b:"fine",c:"overcharge",d:"demurrage"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2015"},{id:196,question:"The following are the methods of claim settlement except",option:{a:"Cash",b:"Repair",c:"Reinstatement",d:"Repayment"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"3"},{id:213,question:"Insurance is a contract that is based on",option:{a:"possibility",b:"probability",c:"positivity",d:"negativity"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"4"},{id:154,question:"---------- is the evidence cover of the risk given to the insured by the insurer",option:{a:"Cover",b:"Policy",c:"Claim",d:"Compensation"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"3"},{id:349,question:"Which of the following factors limits indemnity?",option:{a:"Cession",b:"Re - insurance",c:"Excess",d:"Co - insurance"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2015"},{id:286,question:"The amount given to the insured if he does not want the contract to continue is called",option:{a:"premium",b:"price",c:"consideration",d:"surrender value"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"5"},{id:44,question:"Insurers A and B cover a risk at the ratio of 2:5 for the sum insured of N= 1,800. How much would insurer  A get from the risk?",option:{a:"N= 1,285.00",b:"N= 771.00",c:"N= 514.00",d:"N= 180.00"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2014"},{id:31,question:"A type of reinsurance where cession and acceptance is obligatory is",option:{a:"treaty",b:"captive",c:"facultative",d:"retrocession"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2014"},{id:47,question:"Which of the following is a risk covered in endowment assurance?",option:{a:"Permanent disability",b:"Bodily injury",c:"Temporary disability",d:"Death cover"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2014"},{id:117,question:"There must  be  a  close  connection  between  the loss actually suffered and the risk is relating to the principle  of",option:{a:"Abandonment",b:"Proximate cause",c:"Utmost good faith",d:"Adhesion"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"2"},{id:222,question:"A contract that is contrary to public policy is",option:{a:"valid contract",b:"legal contract",c:"illegal contract",d:"voidable contract"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"4"},{id:337,question:"The  document issued by  the  insurer when there is a change in the particulars of a risk insured is",option:{a:"endorsement",b:"certificate",c:"voucher",d:"policy"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2015"},{id:54,question:"The facts which might influence any party’s willingness to enter the contract or reject it is called",option:{a:"insurable fact",b:"insurance fact",c:"insured fact",d:"material fact"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"1"},{id:93,question:"Subrogation principle can be applied in the following insurance policies except in",option:{a:"aviation policy",b:"engineering policy",c:"life policy",d:"marine policy"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"1"},{id:212,question:"An insurance contract which does not involve mutuality of agreement in which only one of the parties involved in the contract makes promises that are legally binding is called",option:{a:"double contract",b:"single contract",c:"multilateral contract",d:"unilateral contract"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"4"},{id:194,question:"A particular risk which is transferred to another re-insurance under a re-insurance treaty is",option:{a:"Cedant",b:"Cession",c:"Facultative",d:"Cede"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"3"},{id:81,question:"The following are examples of bad moral hazard except",option:{a:"Fraudulent activities",b:"Carelessness",c:"Honesty",d:"Unreasonableness"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"1"},{id:158,question:"The cause of a loss is known as",option:{a:"Peril",b:"Hazard",c:"Loss",d:"Risk"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"3"},{id:98,question:"Engineering insurance covers the following except",option:{a:"boiler explosion",b:"building and civil",c:"business interruption",d:"machinery breakdown"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"model",examyear:"1"}],n={message:e,subject:i,status:200,total:120,data:a};export{a as data,n as default,e as message,o as status,i as subject,t as total};
